Come on, let's go
The snacks look so cute
Hello everyone
Where am I now?
I'm at the Meiji Jingu baseball stadium.
I'm rehearsing the day before the live show today.
I'm going to stay close to the camera for 4 days.
How is it?
There are a lot of dioramas in this set.
I'm wearing an air suit inside.
There are 6th gen players in front of me, their first time at Jingu.
Everyone is preparing for the day off.
Let's do our best in the rehearsal.
Who is it?
What is the name of the player?
I don't know who it is.
I don't know who everyone is.
I am Nagashima.
It's a spy.
Who is it?
I don't know who it is.
We look like monsters
It's already dark.
The rehearsal was completed the day before yesterday.
Yeah!
It was hot, but I came here and I thought it would be a good summer.
I remembered a lot of things as soon as I stood on the stage.
I remembered a lot of things.
I will do my best from tomorrow.
I will eat and sleep.
See you tomorrow.
Good morning.
It's the morning of the first day of the live.
It's a little cloudy.
After this, it's a rain forecast.
I believe that the weather will be good.
I will do my best in the rehearsal.
I will do my best.
We are in the middle of the rehearsal.
It's raining.
It's raining every year.
It will stop by this time.
I want to dance.
She can do anything.
It's 3.48 pm.
It's about two hours before the live show.
It's here.
The earphone and cell phone are in front of Aruno.
I'm checking the choreography.
I fell asleep, this is Nakanishi Aruno san.
Today you have braids!
Cute! Isn't it rare?
I made them with Aya
Is that it? Hey, why don't you invite me?
It's the first day of the live show.
It's here, Sakutan!
What did you check?
Aori of Hadashi De Summer.
Aori practiced. Admirable, right?
I can't say it's cute.
Aori practiced while eating ice cream before the live show.
There are two corners today.
It's the first day of the live show.
Let's practice.
Let's do our best.
I'm going to make my bangs beautiful.
I thought I wouldn't lose.
The wind is strong at Jingu.
I'm going to separate my bangs.
I'm going to use the hair iron.
By the way today, in 2023,
I have seen a picture of Kubo san hairstyle,
and I made it too.
I have some bad news.
There is a nail here.
It's important to hide this.
This is the most important part of my bangs.
I'm done with my bangs.
I'm going to use my bangs today.
Urumin! What are you doing?
I'm doing a lot of memos.
Wow! What kind of memos?
Show me.
Show me your position.
Look! Well done!
You are so diligent.
You're preparing properly for the live show.
Thank you.
Let's do our best.
Are you nervous?
Are you looking forward to it?
I'm looking forward to it.
You're nervous, aren't you?
I'm nervous.
You're very nervous.
You have a thin face.
I'm looking forward to it.
When it comes to the live show, I'm worried.
You are next to each other.
What are you doing before the live show?
I'm curious.
It's like a rehearsal video.
I'm checking it.
Look at this.
Miku is using it.
It's cute.
I'm using it today.
It's too cute.
What is it?
Hello!
It's a T-shirt from the National Tour.
It's from Fukuoka.
Horaay!
I have a question.
One time I was next to Hinano-chan and Shinkansen.
You didn't touch your phone for about two hours.
Didn't eat or sleep.
You sat down and look in front of you for two hours straight.
I always sat down next to her.
When I was in school, Shinkansen was in Shizuoka.
I often rode Shinkansen.
It's like a train.
It's a train.
Everyone knows something.
Are you really just thinking?
I was dancing in my head.
You were dancing.
I'm glad I solved it.
This is the theme of this live show.
Everyone is a heroine.
Look.
There are different colors of tiaras.
We fifth gen are pink.
The fourth generation is orange.
The third generation is light blue.
It's very cute.
The sixth generation is turquoise green.
It's a very fashionable color.
Everyone is lined up in front of each other.
I'm grateful.
He is always writing a lot of MCs.
Is it a close-up camera?
I'm sorry.
What kind of joke is this?
I'm sorry to bother you.
Thank you for today.
Let's do our best.
First day.
Match.
It's been about 20 minutes.
I'm going to the venue now.
Finally, there was an air show.
There is a special history in the air.
I think everyone has a different feeling of tension than usual.
Let's do our best and make the first day a success.
Support each other.
Today's theme is
Let's go.
No-! Gyu-!
Hard work, gratitude, smile.
Uchira, Nogizaka noborizaka, 46!
Boisterous... just her
Be strong!
Let's go
Thank you very much.
I go to the encore!
Ah Actually I'm doing it.
Everyone has been cheering for the encore!
Everyone, let's shout out loud.
Let's cheer up for the encore of Nogizaka-chan.
What?! What's that?
The first day of the tour was over safely.
It rained a little, but it was less than expected.
We had a lot of fun.
Thank you for your support.
I was very happy that we were able to perform on this day.
We will do our best tomorrow.
Thank you for your support.
We look forward to your continued support.
Good morning.
It's raining again today.
We will do our best from the rehearsal morning.
Good morning.
I'm looking forward to the rain.
Do you like the rain?
I wanted to enjoy the rain.
I'm looking forward to it.
I will do my best.
Please cover your face like this on a rainy day.
Thank you for your support today as always.
Can you see a mirror?
It's good to be able to experience a recreation.
Kiyoko is the cutest.
Hiyoko-chan
This is my favorite reason why I like rain in Jingu
I love the raincoats
This yellow is cute
Cute
The second rehearsal is over
I like the rain in Jingu, but
I wonder if I can do a teru teru bozu
We're going to make some teru teru bozu
I'm going to make a head
This is the head
I see
I'm going to make a teru teru bozu
This is my first teru teru bozu
I'm going to make a head
I'm going to make a small head like Sakura-san
Cute
You are making fun of me
The head is so small
So cute
You did a good job
Thank you
So cute
You two did a good job
It's going be really sunny, look
It's a different planet from where it was born
I see, it's cute
So cute
It's so high
It's tall, so it's stuck in a good place
It's so good
The head is heavy
Hey! It's the second day
It's going to start in about 10 minutes
It's a miracle, it's sunny
Thank you
Let's do our best today
I'm nervous
I have a speech today
I'm looking forward to it
I have a lot of gratitude that I can't really convey
Thank you for showing me such a beautiful scenery
This summer, I
Thank you very much for making us, Nogizaka46, heroines
The second day is over
It was raining, but it stopped right before the show
I think I was able to deliver the best live performance today
I'm going to do my best tomorrow too
Good night
Good morning
It's the third morning
It's sunny today
There are no clouds
It's already the end of the rainy season
It rained for two days
It's very hot today
I will do my best
Ume and Yuna are going home
It's a peaceful view
It's the first day
It's going to start in about 10 minutes
How is it?
I thought it was going to end in 6 days
But it's already the third day
It's going to start in a moment
That's right
I'm looking forward to the navel orange
Let's do it together
I will do my best
Have you made your hair? Awesome
It's a cool song today
So I've made a cool hairstyle
Cute and cool
You look more adult
Cat
It's a cat
There is also a cat
The hairstyle is cute
It's rare to have such a long hair
Super idol
It's cute
Let's do our best
Heart
It's cute
I will do my best
How is it?
It's cute ponytail
I thought it would be hot today, after the rain
I tried it
Is it cool?
The neck is very cool
I want to raise it
I'm not confident to show my face
I became a demon again
I finished the third day safely
The weather has been good today
And
Ta-da
There was a live performance on the day of Ayatie's birthday
I was able to celebrate with everyone
I was able to have a fun live
I will leave the rest tomorrow
Be careful
I'm still very energetic
I want to do my best tomorrow
I look forward to it
Good morning
It's the morning of the last day
I don't feel like it's the last day
Come on, cheer up
How was it?
Did you have an accident yesterday?
What is it?
I kissed the real thing
I'm very satisfied
I'm surprised
A little
It was a great success
When I think about it with my partner
How is it?
When did you start talking like that?
Thank you for rehearsing in the heat
The tour is coming to an end in no time
Thanks to all the staff this year
I was able to have fun
I would like to thank the staff who are here
I will do my best with everyone
Thank you for the last
Thank you
Rehearsal is over
I will leave it here
I just have to go to the stage
It's really quick
The show will probably start in an instant
I want to do my best
Today's menu is
Navel orange and shrimp
There is a raw spring roll
It looks delicious
Let's eat one
Wow
It's like a festival
Great
There is something like gummy candy
Mango
Wasabi
Mayonnaise
Cheers
It's a whole candied tangerine
I love candied tangerines
It's delicious
I will eat the navel orange and raw spring roll
Let's eat
What is nervous?
What do you do when you are nervous?
It's delicious
It's refreshing
It's sweet
It's delicious
How is it?
It's refreshing
What is this?
I am sitting in my usual seat
Cute
I want to go for a walk
There is
What was that?
I will change my clothes an hour before the show
I will change my clothes
3, 2, 1
I changed
Cute
It's the last day
I will do my best
I've seen you
Hello
It's my favorite hairstyle
Really?
I'm glad I got it
Let's have fun today
Your ponytail is cute
Thank you
Please call my name
It's Mii-kun, is it?
I don't like Mii-kun
It's Mii-kyun
Someone said it
It's Mii-kun. Is it wrong?
It's not Mii-kyun
Hey, Mii-kun is correct, probably
Mii? Kun, kun!
Like a dog?
What is this?
You made it!
Mii-kun kun...
I'm going
I will do my best
Cute
It's cute
What camera is this?
It's YouTube
Youtube? They'll definitely cut it
Why?
I will use it
Can I see it off?
Let's take it off
I will do my best
Fight!
The four days at Jingu are over
I was shooting
I was waiting for the camera
Let's have fun next summer
Please subscribe to the channel and give us a high rating
Bye bye